

Applicant for:

# Senior Java Developer ~\$1800

Dr.JOY 26 August 2020

## Ngô Anh Tài

✓ ngoanhtai1990@hotmail.com

Main interests: Java, PHP

Kính gửi bộ phận tuyển dụng.

Em là Ngô Anh Tài.

Hiện đang làm lập trình viên ở khối công nghệ ngân hàng Hàng Hải MSB Em được biết công ty đang có nhu cầu tuyển dụng lập trình viên Java, với những kinh nghiệm của mình và những gì công ty yêu cầu, em cảm thấy mình khá phù hợp với vị trí này. Rất mong công ty cho em một cơ hội gặp mặt để em có thể nói nhiều hơn về kinh nghiệm của mình, cũng như có cơ hội tìm hiểu nhiều hơn về công ty.

Em xin chân thành cảm ơn!

# Anh Tai Ngo (Ngô Anh Tài)

Birth date: 04/04/1990

Adress: An Trung, Tan Dan, Soc Son, Ha Noi

Phone: 0973 491 825

Email: ngoanhtai1990@hotmail.com

## **Summary**

Skilled Java developer and team leader with diverse experience utilizing Java tools for client-server environments and fluid understanding of many programming languages including Java. Worked with a large team of GUI and Java developers to maintain and improve company projects. Assisted with disaster recovery environments for critical business applications.

#### **Education**

NIIT

Major: Software Developer

## **Employment History**

#### MSB Bank.

Core and Web Java Developer

April 2018 – Present

 Analysis of user requirements, create and modify block diagrams and logic flowcharts.

Oversee architectural development and software activities

- Assisted with detailed technical designs to develop project-specific programs.
- Strong debugging skills, creative preparation of user-level documentation.
- Expertise in Core Java Technologies, and design and development of web-based application.
- Integrated and modified software systems according to the end user specifications.

#### **EVN Group**

Java Developer

February 2015 - January 2018

- Development of applications and software to increase department efficiency
- Efficiently worked within team from scratching to development of company specific software
- Diagnose and correct errors within code to allow for utilization of applications and allow for connections
- Provide a high level of customer support to remote clients using a support eticketing system
- Experience with streamlining SQL guery generation and data modeling

#### **Telsoft JSC**

Java Developer

2012 - December 2014

- Join to projects of Company with role Deverloper
- Support custommer using System

### **Professional Skills**

Front-end: Html, CSS, JS, Angular.

Back-end: Java core, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Data (JPA, Hibernate),

ActiveMQ.

Database: Oracle, MySQL, MongoDB. OS: Linux (CentOS, Redhat, Ubuntu).

#### **PROJECT**

## **CSS – CREDIT SCORING SYSTEM**

Customer	Modeling - Risk Management
Description	Scoring for credit records base on model type and role of risk management
Contribute in the project	<ul><li>Business analysis.</li><li>Design and development some module.</li><li>Unit test.</li><li>Fix bugs.</li></ul>
Team size	8
My position	Developer
Technologies used	<ul><li>Spring Boot</li><li>Oracle</li><li>AngularJS</li></ul>

## **BANCASSURANCE**

Customer	Insurance division – MSB Bank
Description	Manage and process credit records must have insurance, customer care
Contribute in the project	<ul><li>Business analysis.</li><li>Design and development some module.</li><li>Unit test.</li><li>Fix bugs.</li></ul>
Team size	4
My position	Developer
Technologies used	<ul><li>Spring Boot</li><li>Oracle</li><li>AngularJS</li></ul>

## **COLLATE**

Customer	RB, SME divison – MSB Bank
Description	<ul> <li>Develop a data entry system for asset valuation.</li> <li>Mapping customer asset with the catalog on system.</li> <li>Basic pricing</li> </ul>
Contribute in the project	<ul> <li>Business analysis.</li> <li>Design and development some module.</li> <li>Unit test.</li> <li>Fix bugs.</li> </ul>
Team size	5
My position	Developer
Technologies used	<ul><li>Spring Boot</li><li>Oracle</li><li>AngularJS</li></ul>

## **PMIS**

Customer	Product of EVN
Description	Technical manage of electric grids
Contribute in the project	<ul> <li>Design database for business service.</li> <li>Create interface for enterprise register business service.</li> <li>Create interface for user accept or reject request of enterprise</li> <li>Unit test</li> <li>Fix bug</li> </ul>
Team size	6

My position	Developer
Technologies used	<ul><li>Java.</li><li>Primefaces.</li><li>JPA.</li><li>SglServer.</li></ul>

## **JOBS OPERATOR**

Customer	Product of EVN
Description	Job management, work progress in EVN Group
Contribute in the project	<ul> <li>Design database for business service.</li> <li>Create interface for enterprise register business service.</li> <li>Create interface for user accept or reject request of enterprise</li> <li>Unit test</li> <li>Fix bug</li> </ul>
Team size	5
My position	Developer
Technologies used	<ul><li>Java</li><li>Sql Server</li><li>JPA</li><li>Primefaces</li></ul>

## PORTAL REGISTER FOR PUBLIC SERVICES

Customer	MINISTRY OF INDUSTRY AND TRADE
Description	Register for public services
Contribute in the project	<ul> <li>Design database for business service.</li> <li>Create interface for enterprise register business service.</li> <li>Create interface for user accept or reject request of enterprise</li> <li>Unit test</li> <li>Fix bug</li> </ul>
Team size	8
My position	Developer
Technologies used	<ul><li>Java</li><li>Oracle</li><li>Hibernate</li><li>Primefaces</li><li>Liferay Portal</li></ul>

## **SMS SPAM**

Customer	VNCERT
Description	Project against the sms spam of VNCert.
Technical description	<ul> <li>Using multipe thread socket connect to ports of Simbox.</li> <li>Send AT-Command to simbox</li> <li>Get data response from simbox.</li> <li>Data analysis, get infomation of SMS (sender, content, timesend)</li> <li>Content analysis, check sms is spam or not spam.</li> </ul>
Contribute in the project	<ul> <li>Business analysis.</li> <li>Design and development some module.</li> <li>Unit test.</li> <li>Fix bugs.</li> </ul>
Team size	4
My position	Developer
Technologies used	<ul> <li>Java.</li> <li>Socket.</li> <li>Multiple thread</li> <li>Oracle.</li> <li>JSF.</li> <li>GSM Command.</li> </ul>

## GAD1

Customer	Product of company.
Description	Upgrade website g3g4.vn, service send and receive sms of custommers.
Technical description	<ul> <li>Use multiple thread socket connect and manage Simbox, Simcard.</li> <li>Use socket send command check Sim-card information(account, id, signal quality), send sms, receive sms, recharge for account Sim</li> <li>Design database.</li> <li>Creat interface for user typing sms content and send for multipe contacs.</li> <li>Display sms content receive in interface.</li> </ul>
Contribute in the	- Business analysis.
project	- Design and development some module.
. ,	- Unit test.
	- Fix bugs.
	- Operate
Team size	5
My position	Developer
Technologies used	<ul> <li>Java</li> <li>Socket.</li> <li>Multiple thread.</li> <li>Oracle.</li> <li>JSF.</li> <li>GSM – AT command.</li> </ul>

## **SNMP GATEWAY**

Customer	Product of company
Description	Monitor servers status
Technical description	<ul> <li>Send command check server status using SNMP protocol.</li> <li>Get server information(CPU, RAM, HDD,) then insert to DB.</li> <li>Create interface for user monitor and send command.</li> <li>Get all servers status using SNMP protocol (CPU, RAM, HDD, Network)</li> <li>Create gateway for customer request get info of server</li> <li>Monitoring server status.</li> <li>Create report</li> </ul>
Contribute in the	- Business analysis.
project	- Design and development some module.
	- Unit test.
	- Fix bugs.
	- Operate
Team size	4
My position	Developer
Technologies used	- Java
	- Oracle
	- Birt Report
	- JSF, Primeface
	- Multiple thread